smartproductguide.com 2011-10-04

# Privacy Policy | Smart Product Guide

Privacy Policy

We consider respecting a user's privacy as one of our most significant responsibilities. We created the following privacy policy guidelines with a fundamental respect of your right to privacy.

How We Gather Information

We are in the business of intermediating between consumers who wish to receive highly valuable promotions and offers of goods and services and companies who offer those promotions, goods and services. We only collect the information you voluntarily give us when you register for an offer. At this time we do NOT put "cookies" on your browser. We do NOT track what other sites you visit. Your web activities are confidential to you and we respect your privacy.

We obtain information from our business partners and clients. We mandate that any company that provides us with data certify that the data represents permissible contact data. If we become aware that the data is not in compliance we will terminate our relationship with them immediately.

During registration either here or at our other company owned websites, users are required to give their contact information (such as name, address, e-mail address, cell or phone number). This information is used to contact the user to offer goods and services, if they choose to receive them. It is optional for the user to provide demographic information (such as income level and gender) so that we can provide a more personalized experience for the user. We, or our marketing partners, may, from time to time, append the user's contact information with additional, readily available demographic information so that we can provide a more personalized experience for the user.

How We Use Information

Our marketing partners wishing to contact you either give their client contact information to us and we deliver it to you, or we provide your identity to them so they can deliver messages directly to you. Your shared-interest information is shared through aggregated data, segregated into categories and may be tied to your name. It is solely at your discretion if you choose to provide additional personally identifiable information to a marketer by making a purchase, requesting additional information, or communicating directly with the company or organization after using its website.

When you register at any of our other sites you will receive offers from us or our marketing partners, should you choose to receive them. Our marketing partners, and others, may use this information to make offers to you in your areas of interest or other offers regulated by the Fair Credit Reporting Act. We do not obtain or share credit information about you with anyone. Only we, or our marketing partners, will possess your contact information.

You Can Control the Use of Your Information

At any time during the period you agree to receive offers, you have the right to choose to not receive offers from any of our partners. You can do this by notifying that partner through return e-mail that you wish to not receive such information in the future from that partner. If you wish to opt-out of receiving offers from us, as well, you may do so by clicking on the unsubscribe link you can then enter your email address into the opt out page to be removed.

Surveys & Contests

From time to time our site may request information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information may include contact information (such as name, address, e-mail address, cell or phone number, etc), demographic information (such as age level, zip code) or interest category (such as travel, sports). This information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving satisfaction to the users of the goods and services being offered.

The Use Of Cookies

At this time, we do NOT use "cookies" to collect personal information and we do NOT use cookies to retrieve information from your computer for purposes that are unrelated to the website or your interaction with the website.

Sharing

We currently use several outside companies to execute the marketing campaigns on behalf of some of our marketing partners. We will share your e-mail name or other contact information that is necessary for these third parties to provide these services. These third parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purposes of providing these services.

Security

We utilize the latest server technology to house our database. To protect our database we use a complex system of backups and firewall technology. These technologies are deployed as part of a sophisticated security architecture and protocol. All data resides in a tightly controlled, secure datacenter.

Notification of Changes

If we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify you via email. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post the notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.
